Qasim Karimi

Hi, I am Qasim, a top-rated developer and business owner with over 7 years of experience. I have developed from scratch dozens of sites, customized and extended many sites, implemented CMS systems in the past like WordPress and now I work a lot in Laravel MVC.

EXPERIENCE

Upwork - https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~01dc2a38c26c753852

```
Kabul Municipality — MIS Specialist
```

(Octuber 2020 - April 2023) Company Website: https://km.gov.af

Duty: Team Leader, Develop many MIS

Truth Land Company — Website & Database developer

(March 2013 - Jun 2020) Company Website: <u>tlc-af.com</u>

Duty: Website developer, Database developer

SKILLS

Laravel framework, PHP, Mysql, Bootstrap(Front-end framework), Javascript, jquery, Codeigniter MVC, WordPress, HTML5, CSS3, React js, React native, Linux(ubuntu 20.04 LTS)

EDUCATION

Besat, Tehran Iran - high school

SEPTEMBER 1998 - MAY 2010

Ghargistan, Kabul Afghanistan – Bachelor of Computer science

MARCH 2013 - NOVEMBER 2016

REFERENCE

Get Messiah Pty Ltd

jade@getmessiah.io

Jade Bermingham

+61403897642

Inspiring Vacations

mortezarajabi.af@gmail.com

Morteza Rajabi

+61405890610

Nai NGO

info@nai.org.af

Hr manager(Sayed
Asadullah Mahmoody)

+93774409923

Momtaz company
habib@momtaz.ws

Habib Jawid

+93744523666

Truth land Company

hashemi@tlc-af.com

Sayed Ali Hashemi

+93766551060

Rubik company

hashemi@rubik.af

Ramazan Hashemi

+93784092215

WORK SAMPLE

GitLab Account: https://gitlab.com/qasim.almotech

http://mj-consultant.net/ ,

http://novinsimia.com/,

http://dog-house.ae/,

https://gulzadfoundation.org/,

http://nmi.edu.af,

https://harmonydigital.com/,

http://roydadroz.com/,

http://simex19.com/,

https://applylearning.com/,

http://tlc-af.com/,

http://shop.tlc-af.com,

https://nai.org.af